

ABDUL MUCHTAR ASTRIA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER ♥ KARAWANG, INDONESIA • 081280295238

• DETAILS •

Karawang Indonesia 081280295238 muchtara2m@gmail.com

LINKS

Linkedin

Dribble

° SKILLS °

Node.js

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

React

Redux

Tailwind

Bootstrap

PHP

MySQL

Git

HOBBIES

Design & Art, Photography, Game, Music, Videography

PROFILE

Worked as a Frontend Developer at PT PINS Indonesia with 4 years of experience. Bachelor of Computer Science at Bina Nusantara University. I have the ability to create websites, web apps and mobile apps. I also have the ability to create UI/UX designs.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend Developer at PT PINS Indonesia, Jakarta

January 2021 — Present

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- · Make wireframe and mockup page.
- · Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Slicing mockup based on detailed design specifications.
- Make standard dashboard report in graph format as required.
- Collaborated with backend team members to implement new feature developments.
- Integrate Database with API.

Fullstack Developer at PT PINS Indonesia, Jakarta

August 2018 — January 2021

- Developed and presented findings and solutions to user.
- Design and Normalization Database.
- Implemented websites from concept through deployment.
- Solved complex problems using the latest web technologies.
- Make Single Sign On.
- Authenticate with LDAP.
- Make REST API for team Frontend.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Bina Nusantara University, Jakarta

March 2020 — April 2022

Computer Science - 3.48

Associate Degree, Bogor Agricultural University, Bogor

August 2014 — August 2017

Computer Engineering - 3.14

COURSES COURSES

Mastering Web Development With React & Tailwind CSS, BuildWith Angga January 2021

Full-Stack Laravel & Flutter, BuildWith Angga

January 2022

React JS: Progressive Web Apps, BuildWith Angga September 2021 Bootcamp Complete UI/UX Design: Netflix Steraming App with Figma, BuildWith Angga October 2022 Website Development: Microservices, BuildWith Angga January 2022 React Native Apps Developer, BuildWith Angga March 2021 Belajar Membuat Front-End Web untuk Pemula, Dicoding October 2022 Belajar Dasar Pemrograman JavaScript, Dicoding October 2022 Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web, Dicoding October 2022 Belajar Dasar Visualisasi Data October 2022 Memulai Pemrograman Dengan Python October 2022 UX Design Gestalt, BuildWith Angga April 2021 JavaScript (Intermediate) Certificate, HackerRank November 2022 JavaScript (Basic) Certificate, HackerRank November 2022 CSS, HackerRank November 2022 SQL (Basic), HackerRank November 2022